Christ is the image of God yet unseen
In Him God’s fullness dwells so serene
The perfect imprint of God’s very nature
God’s glory shines, through Jesus the Savior
He is the God-Son above all creation
All things were made by, through and for Him
Sustaining the cosmos in full preservation
The word of His power shall never grow dim
Christ is supreme over all beings
God of glory, Lord of kings
Magnificent Savior, creation sings
Christ is supreme
We were his foes, suppressing his glory
Hostile and proud, rebellious, unworthy
Yet at the cross, he poured out his blood
Redeeming Shepherd, atoning his flock
The grave was defeated, he rose from the dead
Now ruling from heaven, the church’s chief head
Sovereignly reigning, unbeatable Lord
Magnify Jesus, now and forever adored
Christ is supreme over all beings
God of glory, Lord of kings
Magnificent Savior, creation sings
Christ is supreme over all beings
God of glory, Lord of kings
Magnificent Savior, creation sings
Christ is supreme